[Music]
i visited the town of squim last week
during the annual lavender festival
it seems like the entire town exploded
into shades of purple and green
overnight
the smell was everywhere even while
driving i could detect it and it led me
to this quaint little farm just outside
of town
[Music]
do
i also got the chance to spend a day at
an adorable little cottage by the sea
my boyfriend and i made a single
exception of staying at a family home to
enjoy our first ever bnb
it felt appropriate to do something a
bit fancy as a treat to celebrate two
years of knowing each other
we're not often travelers and it was so
exciting
the biggest struggle i faced during this
trip was actually disconnecting from my
work life
i find that very difficult to do and it
was a wonderful challenge to truly
embrace the days
i can't remember the last time i had a
proper vacation planned out like this
of course i still filmed and did what
was necessary to keep my business
running but for the most part i had a
lot more time off than usual
it was so lovely to take joy in soaking
in the sights and sounds of a new place
the luscious greens of the landscape
made me miss springtime at home
and look forward to the autumn reigns
it's so easy to get caught up in work
especially when you enjoy your job or
have big goals for the future
a current dream of mine is to be a
homeowner in my mind's eye i've always
imagined having a family and living in a
small cabin by the river or nestled deep
in a forest
but i find that the quickest way to turn
a dream into something stressful is by
setting a strict timeline to its
achievement
if i do that it inevitably becomes a
sort of race where my body exists in the
present but my mind lives in the future
imagining a life i don't have while
letting the one i do pass me by
[Music]
i find this mentality can negatively
affect everything in life
for example i've always been a dreamer
and someone with a vivid imagination and
yet it is important to not let that
blind you from appreciating the tactile
world
the people in your life your real
relationships
these things solely existing in the
present at this very moment have so much
value
and if i've learned anything this summer
it's that your life can change in the
blink of an eye
you may very well lose something
important when you least expect it
that is the beautiful and complex and
heart-wrenching reality
you cannot control the future but right
now at this moment
you can choose to love
and there's no better way to use your
time
[Music]
as i enjoy the last days of my trip and
prepare to head home i realized that
even though i've loved this vacation
it also made me aware of how much i
truly feel tied to my valley
even with everything that's going on and
what it's facing right now i want to be
there and to do what i can to protect it
it's a cathartic moment when you realize
you've truly found home
i hope you all have a wonderful day or
night i'm sending you my love and i will
see you next week
[Music]
you